<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Entity parent="template_unit_champion_infantry_swordsman">
  <Identity>
    <Civ>sele</Civ>
    <Lang>greek</Lang>
    <GenericName>Romanized Heavy Swordsman</GenericName>
    <SpecificName>Thorakitès Rhomaïkós</SpecificName>
    <History>In 166 BC, at the Daphne Parade under Antiochus IV, the Argyraspides corps is only seen to be 5,000 strong. However 5,000 troops armed in the Roman fashion are present and they are described as being in the prime of their life, perhaps denoting their elite nature. It is possible that the missing 5,000 men of the Argyraspides were the 5,000 'Romanized' infantry marching alongside them. The training of a segment of the royal guard in 'Roman' methods was probably down to several factors. Firstly, Antiochus IV had spent part of his early life in Rome and had acquired rather an excessive admiration for Rome's power and methods. Secondly, the future wars that the Seleucids might be fighting would probably be in the Eastern satrapies against mobile enemies and other large areas of land. Training troops in this way would add to the overall efficiency and capability of the army and make it more maneuverable. Indeed, the 'Romanized' troops are seen facing the Maccabees at the Battle of Beth Zechariah in 162 BC. Thirdly, the defeat of the Macedonian Antigonids at the Battle of Pydna in 168 BC was a great culture shock, showing the complete destruction of the Macedonian military system at the hands of the Roman legion. It has been suggested that the fact that these 5,000 men are marching at the head of the army was meant to show Antiochus IV's intention of reforming the entire Seleucid army along Roman lines, though whether or not this complete reform actually took place is unknown. The true extent of the adoption of Roman techniques is unknown, some have suggested that the infantry are in fact more likely to be Thureophoroi or Thorakitai, troops armed with an oval shield of the Celtic type, a thrusting spear and javelins.</History>
    <Icon>units/sele_champion_swordsman.png</Icon>
    <RequiredTechnology>successors/unlock_reform_army</RequiredTechnology>
  </Identity>
  <VisualActor>
    <Actor>units/seleucids/champion_infantry_swordsman.xml</Actor>
  </VisualActor>
</Entity>
