Basic Latin and Latin-1 Supplement characters, for use as input to the Font Builder:

0020:   SPACE
0021: ! EXCLAMATION MARK
0022: " QUOTATION MARK
0023: # NUMBER SIGN
0024: $ DOLLAR SIGN
0025: % PERCENT SIGN
0026: & AMPERSAND
0027: ' APOSTROPHE
0028: ( LEFT PARENTHESIS
0029: ) RIGHT PARENTHESIS
002A: * ASTERISK
002B: + PLUS SIGN
002C: , COMMA
002D: - HYPHEN-MINUS
002E: . FULL STOP
002F: / SOLIDUS
0030: 0 DIGIT ZERO
0031: 1 DIGIT ONE
0032: 2 DIGIT TWO
0033: 3 DIGIT THREE
0034: 4 DIGIT FOUR
0035: 5 DIGIT FIVE
0036: 6 DIGIT SIX
0037: 7 DIGIT SEVEN
0038: 8 DIGIT EIGHT
0039: 9 DIGIT NINE
003A: : COLON
003B: ; SEMICOLON
003C: < LESS-THAN SIGN
003D: = EQUALS SIGN
003E: > GREATER-THAN SIGN
003F: ? QUESTION MARK
0040: @ COMMERCIAL AT
0041: A LATIN CAPITAL LETTER A
0042: B LATIN CAPITAL LETTER B
0043: C LATIN CAPITAL LETTER C
0044: D LATIN CAPITAL LETTER D
0045: E LATIN CAPITAL LETTER E
0046: F LATIN CAPITAL LETTER F
0047: G LATIN CAPITAL LETTER G
0048: H LATIN CAPITAL LETTER H
0049: I LATIN CAPITAL LETTER I
004A: J LATIN CAPITAL LETTER J
004B: K LATIN CAPITAL LETTER K
004C: L LATIN CAPITAL LETTER L
004D: M LATIN CAPITAL LETTER M
004E: N LATIN CAPITAL LETTER N
004F: O LATIN CAPITAL LETTER O
0050: P LATIN CAPITAL LETTER P
0051: Q LATIN CAPITAL LETTER Q
0052: R LATIN CAPITAL LETTER R
0053: S LATIN CAPITAL LETTER S
0054: T LATIN CAPITAL LETTER T
0055: U LATIN CAPITAL LETTER U
0056: V LATIN CAPITAL LETTER V
0057: W LATIN CAPITAL LETTER W
0058: X LATIN CAPITAL LETTER X
0059: Y LATIN CAPITAL LETTER Y
005A: Z LATIN CAPITAL LETTER Z
005B: [ LEFT SQUARE BRACKET
005C: \ REVERSE SOLIDUS
005D: ] RIGHT SQUARE BRACKET
005E: ^ CIRCUMFLEX ACCENT
005F: _ LOW LINE
0060: ` GRAVE ACCENT
0061: a LATIN SMALL LETTER A
0062: b LATIN SMALL LETTER B
0063: c LATIN SMALL LETTER C
0064: d LATIN SMALL LETTER D
0065: e LATIN SMALL LETTER E
0066: f LATIN SMALL LETTER F
0067: g LATIN SMALL LETTER G
0068: h LATIN SMALL LETTER H
0069: i LATIN SMALL LETTER I
006A: j LATIN SMALL LETTER J
006B: k LATIN SMALL LETTER K
006C: l LATIN SMALL LETTER L
006D: m LATIN SMALL LETTER M
006E: n LATIN SMALL LETTER N
006F: o LATIN SMALL LETTER O
0070: p LATIN SMALL LETTER P
0071: q LATIN SMALL LETTER Q
0072: r LATIN SMALL LETTER R
0073: s LATIN SMALL LETTER S
0074: t LATIN SMALL LETTER T
0075: u LATIN SMALL LETTER U
0076: v LATIN SMALL LETTER V
0077: w LATIN SMALL LETTER W
0078: x LATIN SMALL LETTER X
0079: y LATIN SMALL LETTER Y
007A: z LATIN SMALL LETTER Z
007B: { LEFT CURLY BRACKET
007C: | VERTICAL LINE
007D: } RIGHT CURLY BRACKET
007E: ~ TILDE
00A1: ¡ INVERTED EXCLAMATION MARK
00A2: ¢ CENT SIGN
00A3: £ POUND SIGN
00A4: ¤ CURRENCY SIGN
00A5: ¥ YEN SIGN
00A6: ¦ BROKEN BAR
00A7: § SECTION SIGN
00A8: ¨ DIAERESIS
00A9: © COPYRIGHT SIGN
00AA: ª FEMININE ORDINAL INDICATOR
00AB: « LEFT-POINTING DOUBLE ANGLE QUOTATION MARK
00AC: ¬ NOT SIGN
00AD: ­ SOFT HYPHEN
00AE: ® REGISTERED SIGN
00AF: ¯ MACRON
00B0: ° DEGREE SIGN
00B1: ± PLUS-MINUS SIGN
00B2: ² SUPERSCRIPT TWO
00B3: ³ SUPERSCRIPT THREE
00B4: ´ ACUTE ACCENT
00B5: µ MICRO SIGN
00B6: ¶ PILCROW SIGN
00B7: · MIDDLE DOT
00B8: ¸ CEDILLA
00B9: ¹ SUPERSCRIPT ONE
00BA: º MASCULINE ORDINAL INDICATOR
00BB: » RIGHT-POINTING DOUBLE ANGLE QUOTATION MARK
00BC: ¼ VULGAR FRACTION ONE QUARTER
00BD: ½ VULGAR FRACTION ONE HALF
00BE: ¾ VULGAR FRACTION THREE QUARTERS
00BF: ¿ INVERTED QUESTION MARK
00C0: À LATIN CAPITAL LETTER A WITH GRAVE
00C1: Á LATIN CAPITAL LETTER A WITH ACUTE
00C2: Â LATIN CAPITAL LETTER A WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00C3: Ã LATIN CAPITAL LETTER A WITH TILDE
00C4: Ä LATIN CAPITAL LETTER A WITH DIAERESIS
00C5: Å LATIN CAPITAL LETTER A WITH RING ABOVE
00C6: Æ LATIN CAPITAL LETTER AE
00C7: Ç LATIN CAPITAL LETTER C WITH CEDILLA
00C8: È LATIN CAPITAL LETTER E WITH GRAVE
00C9: É LATIN CAPITAL LETTER E WITH ACUTE
00CA: Ê LATIN CAPITAL LETTER E WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00CB: Ë LATIN CAPITAL LETTER E WITH DIAERESIS
00CC: Ì LATIN CAPITAL LETTER I WITH GRAVE
00CD: Í LATIN CAPITAL LETTER I WITH ACUTE
00CE: Î LATIN CAPITAL LETTER I WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00CF: Ï LATIN CAPITAL LETTER I WITH DIAERESIS
00D0: Ð LATIN CAPITAL LETTER ETH
00D1: Ñ LATIN CAPITAL LETTER N WITH TILDE
00D2: Ò LATIN CAPITAL LETTER O WITH GRAVE
00D3: Ó LATIN CAPITAL LETTER O WITH ACUTE
00D4: Ô LATIN CAPITAL LETTER O WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00D5: Õ LATIN CAPITAL LETTER O WITH TILDE
00D6: Ö LATIN CAPITAL LETTER O WITH DIAERESIS
00D7: × MULTIPLICATION SIGN
00D8: Ø LATIN CAPITAL LETTER O WITH STROKE
00D9: Ù LATIN CAPITAL LETTER U WITH GRAVE
00DA: Ú LATIN CAPITAL LETTER U WITH ACUTE
00DB: Û LATIN CAPITAL LETTER U WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00DC: Ü LATIN CAPITAL LETTER U WITH DIAERESIS
00DD: Ý LATIN CAPITAL LETTER Y WITH ACUTE
00DE: Þ LATIN CAPITAL LETTER THORN
00DF: ß LATIN SMALL LETTER SHARP S
00E0: à LATIN SMALL LETTER A WITH GRAVE
00E1: á LATIN SMALL LETTER A WITH ACUTE
00E2: â LATIN SMALL LETTER A WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00E3: ã LATIN SMALL LETTER A WITH TILDE
00E4: ä LATIN SMALL LETTER A WITH DIAERESIS
00E5: å LATIN SMALL LETTER A WITH RING ABOVE
00E6: æ LATIN SMALL LETTER AE
00E7: ç LATIN SMALL LETTER C WITH CEDILLA
00E8: è LATIN SMALL LETTER E WITH GRAVE
00E9: é LATIN SMALL LETTER E WITH ACUTE
00EA: ê LATIN SMALL LETTER E WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00EB: ë LATIN SMALL LETTER E WITH DIAERESIS
00EC: ì LATIN SMALL LETTER I WITH GRAVE
00ED: í LATIN SMALL LETTER I WITH ACUTE
00EE: î LATIN SMALL LETTER I WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00EF: ï LATIN SMALL LETTER I WITH DIAERESIS
00F0: ð LATIN SMALL LETTER ETH
00F1: ñ LATIN SMALL LETTER N WITH TILDE
00F2: ò LATIN SMALL LETTER O WITH GRAVE
00F3: ó LATIN SMALL LETTER O WITH ACUTE
00F4: ô LATIN SMALL LETTER O WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00F5: õ LATIN SMALL LETTER O WITH TILDE
00F6: ö LATIN SMALL LETTER O WITH DIAERESIS
00F7: ÷ DIVISION SIGN
00F8: ø LATIN SMALL LETTER O WITH STROKE
00F9: ù LATIN SMALL LETTER U WITH GRAVE
00FA: ú LATIN SMALL LETTER U WITH ACUTE
00FB: û LATIN SMALL LETTER U WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00FC: ü LATIN SMALL LETTER U WITH DIAERESIS
00FD: ý LATIN SMALL LETTER Y WITH ACUTE
00FE: þ LATIN SMALL LETTER THORN
00FF: ÿ LATIN SMALL LETTER Y WITH DIAERESIS