Basic Latin, Latin-1 Supplement, Greek, Cyrillic, and Hebrew
characters, for use as input to the Font Builder:

0020:    SPACE
0021: !  EXCLAMATION MARK
0022: "  QUOTATION MARK
0023: #  NUMBER SIGN
0024: $  DOLLAR SIGN
0025: %  PERCENT SIGN
0026: &  AMPERSAND
0027: '  APOSTROPHE
0028: (  LEFT PARENTHESIS
0029: )  RIGHT PARENTHESIS
002A: *  ASTERISK
002B: +  PLUS SIGN
002C: ,  COMMA
002D: -  HYPHEN-MINUS
002E: .  FULL STOP
002F: /  SOLIDUS
0030: 0  DIGIT ZERO
0031: 1  DIGIT ONE
0032: 2  DIGIT TWO
0033: 3  DIGIT THREE
0034: 4  DIGIT FOUR
0035: 5  DIGIT FIVE
0036: 6  DIGIT SIX
0037: 7  DIGIT SEVEN
0038: 8  DIGIT EIGHT
0039: 9  DIGIT NINE
003A: :  COLON
003B: ;  SEMICOLON
003C: <  LESS-THAN SIGN
003D: =  EQUALS SIGN
003E: >  GREATER-THAN SIGN
003F: ?  QUESTION MARK
0040: @  COMMERCIAL AT
0041: A  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER A
0042: B  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER B
0043: C  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER C
0044: D  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER D
0045: E  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER E
0046: F  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER F
0047: G  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER G
0048: H  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER H
0049: I  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER I
004A: J  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER J
004B: K  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER K
004C: L  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER L
004D: M  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER M
004E: N  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER N
004F: O  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER O
0050: P  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER P
0051: Q  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER Q
0052: R  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER R
0053: S  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER S
0054: T  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER T
0055: U  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER U
0056: V  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER V
0057: W  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER W
0058: X  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER X
0059: Y  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER Y
005A: Z  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER Z
005B: [  LEFT SQUARE BRACKET
005C: \  REVERSE SOLIDUS
005D: ]  RIGHT SQUARE BRACKET
005E: ^  CIRCUMFLEX ACCENT
005F: _  LOW LINE
0060: `  GRAVE ACCENT
0061: a  LATIN SMALL LETTER A
0062: b  LATIN SMALL LETTER B
0063: c  LATIN SMALL LETTER C
0064: d  LATIN SMALL LETTER D
0065: e  LATIN SMALL LETTER E
0066: f  LATIN SMALL LETTER F
0067: g  LATIN SMALL LETTER G
0068: h  LATIN SMALL LETTER H
0069: i  LATIN SMALL LETTER I
006A: j  LATIN SMALL LETTER J
006B: k  LATIN SMALL LETTER K
006C: l  LATIN SMALL LETTER L
006D: m  LATIN SMALL LETTER M
006E: n  LATIN SMALL LETTER N
006F: o  LATIN SMALL LETTER O
0070: p  LATIN SMALL LETTER P
0071: q  LATIN SMALL LETTER Q
0072: r  LATIN SMALL LETTER R
0073: s  LATIN SMALL LETTER S
0074: t  LATIN SMALL LETTER T
0075: u  LATIN SMALL LETTER U
0076: v  LATIN SMALL LETTER V
0077: w  LATIN SMALL LETTER W
0078: x  LATIN SMALL LETTER X
0079: y  LATIN SMALL LETTER Y
007A: z  LATIN SMALL LETTER Z
007B: {  LEFT CURLY BRACKET
007C: |  VERTICAL LINE
007D: }  RIGHT CURLY BRACKET
007E: ~  TILDE
007F:   <control>
0080:   <control>
0081:   <control>
0082:   <control>
0083:   <control>
0084:   <control>
0085:   <control>
0086:   <control>
0087:   <control>
0088:   <control>
0089:   <control>
008A:   <control>
008B:   <control>
008C:   <control>
008D:   <control>
008E:   <control>
008F:   <control>
0090:   <control>
0091:   <control>
0092:   <control>
0093:   <control>
0094:   <control>
0095:   <control>
0096:   <control>
0097:   <control>
0098:   <control>
0099:   <control>
009A:   <control>
009B:   <control>
009C:   <control>
009D:   <control>
009E:   <control>
009F:   <control>
00A0:    NO-BREAK SPACE
00A1: ¡  INVERTED EXCLAMATION MARK
00A2: ¢  CENT SIGN
00A3: £  POUND SIGN
00A4: ¤  CURRENCY SIGN
00A5: ¥  YEN SIGN
00A6: ¦  BROKEN BAR
00A7: §  SECTION SIGN
00A8: ¨  DIAERESIS
00A9: ©  COPYRIGHT SIGN
00AA: ª  FEMININE ORDINAL INDICATOR
00AB: «  LEFT-POINTING DOUBLE ANGLE QUOTATION MARK
00AC: ¬  NOT SIGN
00AD: ­  SOFT HYPHEN
00AE: ®  REGISTERED SIGN
00AF: ¯  MACRON
00B0: °  DEGREE SIGN
00B1: ±  PLUS-MINUS SIGN
00B2: ²  SUPERSCRIPT TWO
00B3: ³  SUPERSCRIPT THREE
00B4: ´  ACUTE ACCENT
00B5: µ  MICRO SIGN
00B6: ¶  PILCROW SIGN
00B7: ·  MIDDLE DOT
00B8: ¸  CEDILLA
00B9: ¹  SUPERSCRIPT ONE
00BA: º  MASCULINE ORDINAL INDICATOR
00BB: »  RIGHT-POINTING DOUBLE ANGLE QUOTATION MARK
00BC: ¼  VULGAR FRACTION ONE QUARTER
00BD: ½  VULGAR FRACTION ONE HALF
00BE: ¾  VULGAR FRACTION THREE QUARTERS
00BF: ¿  INVERTED QUESTION MARK
00C0: À  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER A WITH GRAVE
00C1: Á  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER A WITH ACUTE
00C2: Â  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER A WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00C3: Ã  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER A WITH TILDE
00C4: Ä  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER A WITH DIAERESIS
00C5: Å  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER A WITH RING ABOVE
00C6: Æ  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER AE
00C7: Ç  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER C WITH CEDILLA
00C8: È  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER E WITH GRAVE
00C9: É  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER E WITH ACUTE
00CA: Ê  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER E WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00CB: Ë  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER E WITH DIAERESIS
00CC: Ì  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER I WITH GRAVE
00CD: Í  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER I WITH ACUTE
00CE: Î  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER I WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00CF: Ï  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER I WITH DIAERESIS
00D0: Ð  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER ETH
00D1: Ñ  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER N WITH TILDE
00D2: Ò  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER O WITH GRAVE
00D3: Ó  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER O WITH ACUTE
00D4: Ô  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER O WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00D5: Õ  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER O WITH TILDE
00D6: Ö  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER O WITH DIAERESIS
00D7: ×  MULTIPLICATION SIGN
00D8: Ø  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER O WITH STROKE
00D9: Ù  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER U WITH GRAVE
00DA: Ú  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER U WITH ACUTE
00DB: Û  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER U WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00DC: Ü  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER U WITH DIAERESIS
00DD: Ý  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER Y WITH ACUTE
00DE: Þ  LATIN CAPITAL LETTER THORN
00DF: ß  LATIN SMALL LETTER SHARP S
00E0: à  LATIN SMALL LETTER A WITH GRAVE
00E1: á  LATIN SMALL LETTER A WITH ACUTE
00E2: â  LATIN SMALL LETTER A WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00E3: ã  LATIN SMALL LETTER A WITH TILDE
00E4: ä  LATIN SMALL LETTER A WITH DIAERESIS
00E5: å  LATIN SMALL LETTER A WITH RING ABOVE
00E6: æ  LATIN SMALL LETTER AE
00E7: ç  LATIN SMALL LETTER C WITH CEDILLA
00E8: è  LATIN SMALL LETTER E WITH GRAVE
00E9: é  LATIN SMALL LETTER E WITH ACUTE
00EA: ê  LATIN SMALL LETTER E WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00EB: ë  LATIN SMALL LETTER E WITH DIAERESIS
00EC: ì  LATIN SMALL LETTER I WITH GRAVE
00ED: í  LATIN SMALL LETTER I WITH ACUTE
00EE: î  LATIN SMALL LETTER I WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00EF: ï  LATIN SMALL LETTER I WITH DIAERESIS
00F0: ð  LATIN SMALL LETTER ETH
00F1: ñ  LATIN SMALL LETTER N WITH TILDE
00F2: ò  LATIN SMALL LETTER O WITH GRAVE
00F3: ó  LATIN SMALL LETTER O WITH ACUTE
00F4: ô  LATIN SMALL LETTER O WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00F5: õ  LATIN SMALL LETTER O WITH TILDE
00F6: ö  LATIN SMALL LETTER O WITH DIAERESIS
00F7: ÷  DIVISION SIGN
00F8: ø  LATIN SMALL LETTER O WITH STROKE
00F9: ù  LATIN SMALL LETTER U WITH GRAVE
00FA: ú  LATIN SMALL LETTER U WITH ACUTE
00FB: û  LATIN SMALL LETTER U WITH CIRCUMFLEX
00FC: ü  LATIN SMALL LETTER U WITH DIAERESIS
00FD: ý  LATIN SMALL LETTER Y WITH ACUTE
00FE: þ  LATIN SMALL LETTER THORN
00FF: ÿ  LATIN SMALL LETTER Y WITH DIAERESIS

0374: ʹ  GREEK NUMERAL SIGN
0375: ͵  GREEK LOWER NUMERAL SIGN
037A: ͺ  GREEK YPOGEGRAMMENI
037E: ;  GREEK QUESTION MARK
0384: ΄  GREEK TONOS
0385: ΅  GREEK DIALYTIKA TONOS
0386: Ά  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER ALPHA WITH TONOS
0387: ·  GREEK ANO TELEIA
0388: Έ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER EPSILON WITH TONOS
0389: Ή  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER ETA WITH TONOS
038A: Ί  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER IOTA WITH TONOS
038C: Ό  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER OMICRON WITH TONOS
038E: Ύ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER UPSILON WITH TONOS
038F: Ώ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER OMEGA WITH TONOS
0390: ΐ  GREEK SMALL LETTER IOTA WITH DIALYTIKA AND TONOS
0391: Α  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER ALPHA
0392: Β  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER BETA
0393: Γ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER GAMMA
0394: Δ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER DELTA
0395: Ε  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER EPSILON
0396: Ζ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER ZETA
0397: Η  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER ETA
0398: Θ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER THETA
0399: Ι  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER IOTA
039A: Κ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER KAPPA
039B: Λ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER LAMDA
039C: Μ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER MU
039D: Ν  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER NU
039E: Ξ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER XI
039F: Ο  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER OMICRON
03A0: Π  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER PI
03A1: Ρ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER RHO
03A3: Σ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER SIGMA
03A4: Τ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER TAU
03A5: Υ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER UPSILON
03A6: Φ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER PHI
03A7: Χ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER CHI
03A8: Ψ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER PSI
03A9: Ω  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER OMEGA
03AA: Ϊ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER IOTA WITH DIALYTIKA
03AB: Ϋ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER UPSILON WITH DIALYTIKA
03AC: ά  GREEK SMALL LETTER ALPHA WITH TONOS
03AD: έ  GREEK SMALL LETTER EPSILON WITH TONOS
03AE: ή  GREEK SMALL LETTER ETA WITH TONOS
03AF: ί  GREEK SMALL LETTER IOTA WITH TONOS
03B0: ΰ  GREEK SMALL LETTER UPSILON WITH DIALYTIKA AND TONOS
03B1: α  GREEK SMALL LETTER ALPHA
03B2: β  GREEK SMALL LETTER BETA
03B3: γ  GREEK SMALL LETTER GAMMA
03B4: δ  GREEK SMALL LETTER DELTA
03B5: ε  GREEK SMALL LETTER EPSILON
03B6: ζ  GREEK SMALL LETTER ZETA
03B7: η  GREEK SMALL LETTER ETA
03B8: θ  GREEK SMALL LETTER THETA
03B9: ι  GREEK SMALL LETTER IOTA
03BA: κ  GREEK SMALL LETTER KAPPA
03BB: λ  GREEK SMALL LETTER LAMDA
03BC: μ  GREEK SMALL LETTER MU
03BD: ν  GREEK SMALL LETTER NU
03BE: ξ  GREEK SMALL LETTER XI
03BF: ο  GREEK SMALL LETTER OMICRON
03C0: π  GREEK SMALL LETTER PI
03C1: ρ  GREEK SMALL LETTER RHO
03C2: ς  GREEK SMALL LETTER FINAL SIGMA
03C3: σ  GREEK SMALL LETTER SIGMA
03C4: τ  GREEK SMALL LETTER TAU
03C5: υ  GREEK SMALL LETTER UPSILON
03C6: φ  GREEK SMALL LETTER PHI
03C7: χ  GREEK SMALL LETTER CHI
03C8: ψ  GREEK SMALL LETTER PSI
03C9: ω  GREEK SMALL LETTER OMEGA
03CA: ϊ  GREEK SMALL LETTER IOTA WITH DIALYTIKA
03CB: ϋ  GREEK SMALL LETTER UPSILON WITH DIALYTIKA
03CC: ό  GREEK SMALL LETTER OMICRON WITH TONOS
03CD: ύ  GREEK SMALL LETTER UPSILON WITH TONOS
03CE: ώ  GREEK SMALL LETTER OMEGA WITH TONOS
03D0: ϐ  GREEK BETA SYMBOL
03D1: ϑ  GREEK THETA SYMBOL
03D2: ϒ  GREEK UPSILON WITH HOOK SYMBOL
03D3: ϓ  GREEK UPSILON WITH ACUTE AND HOOK SYMBOL
03D4: ϔ  GREEK UPSILON WITH DIAERESIS AND HOOK SYMBOL
03D5: ϕ  GREEK PHI SYMBOL
03D6: ϖ  GREEK PI SYMBOL
03D7: ϗ  GREEK KAI SYMBOL
03D8: Ϙ  GREEK LETTER ARCHAIC KOPPA
03D9: ϙ  GREEK SMALL LETTER ARCHAIC KOPPA
03DA: Ϛ  GREEK LETTER STIGMA
03DB: ϛ  GREEK SMALL LETTER STIGMA
03DC: Ϝ  GREEK LETTER DIGAMMA
03DD: ϝ  GREEK SMALL LETTER DIGAMMA
03DE: Ϟ  GREEK LETTER KOPPA
03DF: ϟ  GREEK SMALL LETTER KOPPA
03E0: Ϡ  GREEK LETTER SAMPI
03E1: ϡ  GREEK SMALL LETTER SAMPI
03E2: Ϣ  COPTIC CAPITAL LETTER SHEI
03E3: ϣ  COPTIC SMALL LETTER SHEI
03E4: Ϥ  COPTIC CAPITAL LETTER FEI
03E5: ϥ  COPTIC SMALL LETTER FEI
03E6: Ϧ  COPTIC CAPITAL LETTER KHEI
03E7: ϧ  COPTIC SMALL LETTER KHEI
03E8: Ϩ  COPTIC CAPITAL LETTER HORI
03E9: ϩ  COPTIC SMALL LETTER HORI
03EA: Ϫ  COPTIC CAPITAL LETTER GANGIA
03EB: ϫ  COPTIC SMALL LETTER GANGIA
03EC: Ϭ  COPTIC CAPITAL LETTER SHIMA
03ED: ϭ  COPTIC SMALL LETTER SHIMA
03EE: Ϯ  COPTIC CAPITAL LETTER DEI
03EF: ϯ  COPTIC SMALL LETTER DEI
03F0: ϰ  GREEK KAPPA SYMBOL
03F1: ϱ  GREEK RHO SYMBOL
03F2: ϲ  GREEK LUNATE SIGMA SYMBOL
03F3: ϳ  GREEK LETTER YOT
03F4: ϴ  GREEK CAPITAL THETA SYMBOL
03F5: ϵ  GREEK LUNATE EPSILON SYMBOL
03F6: ϶  GREEK REVERSED LUNATE EPSILON SYMBOL
03F7: Ϸ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER SHO
03F8: ϸ  GREEK SMALL LETTER SHO
03F9: Ϲ  GREEK CAPITAL LUNATE SIGMA SYMBOL
03FA: Ϻ  GREEK CAPITAL LETTER SAN
03FB: ϻ  GREEK SMALL LETTER SAN

0400: Ѐ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER IE WITH GRAVE
0401: Ё  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER IO
0402: Ђ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER DJE
0403: Ѓ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER GJE
0404: Є  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER UKRAINIAN IE
0405: Ѕ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER DZE
0406: І  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER BYELORUSSIAN-UKRAINIAN I
0407: Ї  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER YI
0408: Ј  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER JE
0409: Љ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER LJE
040A: Њ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER NJE
040B: Ћ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER TSHE
040C: Ќ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER KJE
040D: Ѝ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER I WITH GRAVE
040E: Ў  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER SHORT U
040F: Џ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER DZHE
0410: А  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER A
0411: Б  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER BE
0412: В  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER VE
0413: Г  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER GHE
0414: Д  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER DE
0415: Е  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER IE
0416: Ж  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER ZHE
0417: З  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER ZE
0418: И  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER I
0419: Й  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER SHORT I
041A: К  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER KA
041B: Л  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER EL
041C: М  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER EM
041D: Н  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER EN
041E: О  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER O
041F: П  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER PE
0420: Р  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER ER
0421: С  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER ES
0422: Т  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER TE
0423: У  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER U
0424: Ф  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER EF
0425: Х  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER HA
0426: Ц  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER TSE
0427: Ч  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER CHE
0428: Ш  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER SHA
0429: Щ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER SHCHA
042A: Ъ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER HARD SIGN
042B: Ы  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER YERU
042C: Ь  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER SOFT SIGN
042D: Э  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER E
042E: Ю  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER YU
042F: Я  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER YA
0430: а  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER A
0431: б  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER BE
0432: в  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER VE
0433: г  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER GHE
0434: д  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER DE
0435: е  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER IE
0436: ж  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER ZHE
0437: з  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER ZE
0438: и  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER I
0439: й  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER SHORT I
043A: к  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER KA
043B: л  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER EL
043C: м  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER EM
043D: н  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER EN
043E: о  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER O
043F: п  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER PE
0440: р  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER ER
0441: с  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER ES
0442: т  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER TE
0443: у  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER U
0444: ф  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER EF
0445: х  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER HA
0446: ц  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER TSE
0447: ч  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER CHE
0448: ш  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER SHA
0449: щ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER SHCHA
044A: ъ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER HARD SIGN
044B: ы  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER YERU
044C: ь  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER SOFT SIGN
044D: э  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER E
044E: ю  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER YU
044F: я  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER YA
0450: ѐ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER IE WITH GRAVE
0451: ё  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER IO
0452: ђ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER DJE
0453: ѓ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER GJE
0454: є  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER UKRAINIAN IE
0455: ѕ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER DZE
0456: і  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER BYELORUSSIAN-UKRAINIAN I
0457: ї  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER YI
0458: ј  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER JE
0459: љ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER LJE
045A: њ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER NJE
045B: ћ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER TSHE
045C: ќ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER KJE
045D: ѝ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER I WITH GRAVE
045E: ў  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER SHORT U
045F: џ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER DZHE
0460: Ѡ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER OMEGA
0461: ѡ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER OMEGA
0462: Ѣ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER YAT
0463: ѣ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER YAT
0464: Ѥ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER IOTIFIED E
0465: ѥ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER IOTIFIED E
0466: Ѧ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER LITTLE YUS
0467: ѧ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER LITTLE YUS
0468: Ѩ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER IOTIFIED LITTLE YUS
0469: ѩ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER IOTIFIED LITTLE YUS
046A: Ѫ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER BIG YUS
046B: ѫ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER BIG YUS
046C: Ѭ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER IOTIFIED BIG YUS
046D: ѭ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER IOTIFIED BIG YUS
046E: Ѯ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER KSI
046F: ѯ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER KSI
0470: Ѱ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER PSI
0471: ѱ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER PSI
0472: Ѳ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER FITA
0473: ѳ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER FITA
0474: Ѵ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER IZHITSA
0475: ѵ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER IZHITSA
0476: Ѷ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER IZHITSA WITH DOUBLE GRAVE ACCENT
0477: ѷ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER IZHITSA WITH DOUBLE GRAVE ACCENT
0478: Ѹ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER UK
0479: ѹ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER UK
047A: Ѻ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER ROUND OMEGA
047B: ѻ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER ROUND OMEGA
047C: Ѽ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER OMEGA WITH TITLO
047D: ѽ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER OMEGA WITH TITLO
047E: Ѿ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER OT
047F: ѿ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER OT
0480: Ҁ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER KOPPA
0481: ҁ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER KOPPA
0482: ҂  CYRILLIC THOUSANDS SIGN
0483: ҃  COMBINING CYRILLIC TITLO
0484: ҄  COMBINING CYRILLIC PALATALIZATION
0485: ҅  COMBINING CYRILLIC DASIA PNEUMATA
0486: ҆  COMBINING CYRILLIC PSILI PNEUMATA
0488: ҈  COMBINING CYRILLIC HUNDRED THOUSANDS SIGN
0489: ҉  COMBINING CYRILLIC MILLIONS SIGN
048A: Ҋ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER SHORT I WITH TAIL
048B: ҋ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER SHORT I WITH TAIL
048C: Ҍ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER SEMISOFT SIGN
048D: ҍ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER SEMISOFT SIGN
048E: Ҏ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER ER WITH TICK
048F: ҏ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER ER WITH TICK
0490: Ґ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER GHE WITH UPTURN
0491: ґ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER GHE WITH UPTURN
0492: Ғ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER GHE WITH STROKE
0493: ғ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER GHE WITH STROKE
0494: Ҕ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER GHE WITH MIDDLE HOOK
0495: ҕ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER GHE WITH MIDDLE HOOK
0496: Җ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER ZHE WITH DESCENDER
0497: җ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER ZHE WITH DESCENDER
0498: Ҙ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER ZE WITH DESCENDER
0499: ҙ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER ZE WITH DESCENDER
049A: Қ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER KA WITH DESCENDER
049B: қ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER KA WITH DESCENDER
049C: Ҝ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER KA WITH VERTICAL STROKE
049D: ҝ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER KA WITH VERTICAL STROKE
049E: Ҟ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER KA WITH STROKE
049F: ҟ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER KA WITH STROKE
04A0: Ҡ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER BASHKIR KA
04A1: ҡ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER BASHKIR KA
04A2: Ң  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER EN WITH DESCENDER
04A3: ң  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER EN WITH DESCENDER
04A4: Ҥ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LIGATURE EN GHE
04A5: ҥ  CYRILLIC SMALL LIGATURE EN GHE
04A6: Ҧ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER PE WITH MIDDLE HOOK
04A7: ҧ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER PE WITH MIDDLE HOOK
04A8: Ҩ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER ABKHASIAN HA
04A9: ҩ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER ABKHASIAN HA
04AA: Ҫ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER ES WITH DESCENDER
04AB: ҫ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER ES WITH DESCENDER
04AC: Ҭ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER TE WITH DESCENDER
04AD: ҭ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER TE WITH DESCENDER
04AE: Ү  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER STRAIGHT U
04AF: ү  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER STRAIGHT U
04B0: Ұ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER STRAIGHT U WITH STROKE
04B1: ұ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER STRAIGHT U WITH STROKE
04B2: Ҳ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER HA WITH DESCENDER
04B3: ҳ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER HA WITH DESCENDER
04B4: Ҵ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LIGATURE TE TSE
04B5: ҵ  CYRILLIC SMALL LIGATURE TE TSE
04B6: Ҷ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER CHE WITH DESCENDER
04B7: ҷ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER CHE WITH DESCENDER
04B8: Ҹ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER CHE WITH VERTICAL STROKE
04B9: ҹ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER CHE WITH VERTICAL STROKE
04BA: Һ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER SHHA
04BB: һ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER SHHA
04BC: Ҽ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER ABKHASIAN CHE
04BD: ҽ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER ABKHASIAN CHE
04BE: Ҿ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER ABKHASIAN CHE WITH DESCENDER
04BF: ҿ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER ABKHASIAN CHE WITH DESCENDER
04C0: Ӏ  CYRILLIC LETTER PALOCHKA
04C1: Ӂ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER ZHE WITH BREVE
04C2: ӂ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER ZHE WITH BREVE
04C3: Ӄ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER KA WITH HOOK
04C4: ӄ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER KA WITH HOOK
04C5: Ӆ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER EL WITH TAIL
04C6: ӆ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER EL WITH TAIL
04C7: Ӈ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER EN WITH HOOK
04C8: ӈ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER EN WITH HOOK
04C9: Ӊ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER EN WITH TAIL
04CA: ӊ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER EN WITH TAIL
04CB: Ӌ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER KHAKASSIAN CHE
04CC: ӌ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER KHAKASSIAN CHE
04CD: Ӎ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER EM WITH TAIL
04CE: ӎ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER EM WITH TAIL
04D0: Ӑ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER A WITH BREVE
04D1: ӑ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER A WITH BREVE
04D2: Ӓ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER A WITH DIAERESIS
04D3: ӓ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER A WITH DIAERESIS
04D4: Ӕ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LIGATURE A IE
04D5: ӕ  CYRILLIC SMALL LIGATURE A IE
04D6: Ӗ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER IE WITH BREVE
04D7: ӗ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER IE WITH BREVE
04D8: Ә  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER SCHWA
04D9: ә  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER SCHWA
04DA: Ӛ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER SCHWA WITH DIAERESIS
04DB: ӛ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER SCHWA WITH DIAERESIS
04DC: Ӝ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER ZHE WITH DIAERESIS
04DD: ӝ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER ZHE WITH DIAERESIS
04DE: Ӟ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER ZE WITH DIAERESIS
04DF: ӟ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER ZE WITH DIAERESIS
04E0: Ӡ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER ABKHASIAN DZE
04E1: ӡ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER ABKHASIAN DZE
04E2: Ӣ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER I WITH MACRON
04E3: ӣ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER I WITH MACRON
04E4: Ӥ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER I WITH DIAERESIS
04E5: ӥ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER I WITH DIAERESIS
04E6: Ӧ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER O WITH DIAERESIS
04E7: ӧ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER O WITH DIAERESIS
04E8: Ө  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER BARRED O
04E9: ө  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER BARRED O
04EA: Ӫ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER BARRED O WITH DIAERESIS
04EB: ӫ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER BARRED O WITH DIAERESIS
04EC: Ӭ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER E WITH DIAERESIS
04ED: ӭ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER E WITH DIAERESIS
04EE: Ӯ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER U WITH MACRON
04EF: ӯ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER U WITH MACRON
04F0: Ӱ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER U WITH DIAERESIS
04F1: ӱ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER U WITH DIAERESIS
04F2: Ӳ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER U WITH DOUBLE ACUTE
04F3: ӳ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER U WITH DOUBLE ACUTE
04F4: Ӵ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER CHE WITH DIAERESIS
04F5: ӵ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER CHE WITH DIAERESIS
04F8: Ӹ  CYRILLIC CAPITAL LETTER YERU WITH DIAERESIS
04F9: ӹ  CYRILLIC SMALL LETTER YERU WITH DIAERESIS

0591: ֑  HEBREW ACCENT ETNAHTA
0592: ֒  HEBREW ACCENT SEGOL
0593: ֓  HEBREW ACCENT SHALSHELET
0594: ֔  HEBREW ACCENT ZAQEF QATAN
0595: ֕  HEBREW ACCENT ZAQEF GADOL
0596: ֖  HEBREW ACCENT TIPEHA
0597: ֗  HEBREW ACCENT REVIA
0598: ֘  HEBREW ACCENT ZARQA
0599: ֙  HEBREW ACCENT PASHTA
059A: ֚  HEBREW ACCENT YETIV
059B: ֛  HEBREW ACCENT TEVIR
059C: ֜  HEBREW ACCENT GERESH
059D: ֝  HEBREW ACCENT GERESH MUQDAM
059E: ֞  HEBREW ACCENT GERSHAYIM
059F: ֟  HEBREW ACCENT QARNEY PARA
05A0: ֠  HEBREW ACCENT TELISHA GEDOLA
05A1: ֡  HEBREW ACCENT PAZER
05A3: ֣  HEBREW ACCENT MUNAH
05A4: ֤  HEBREW ACCENT MAHAPAKH
05A5: ֥  HEBREW ACCENT MERKHA
05A6: ֦  HEBREW ACCENT MERKHA KEFULA
05A7: ֧  HEBREW ACCENT DARGA
05A8: ֨  HEBREW ACCENT QADMA
05A9: ֩  HEBREW ACCENT TELISHA QETANA
05AA: ֪  HEBREW ACCENT YERAH BEN YOMO
05AB: ֫  HEBREW ACCENT OLE
05AC: ֬  HEBREW ACCENT ILUY
05AD: ֭  HEBREW ACCENT DEHI
05AE: ֮  HEBREW ACCENT ZINOR
05AF: ֯  HEBREW MARK MASORA CIRCLE
05B0: ְ  HEBREW POINT SHEVA
05B1: ֱ  HEBREW POINT HATAF SEGOL
05B2: ֲ  HEBREW POINT HATAF PATAH
05B3: ֳ  HEBREW POINT HATAF QAMATS
05B4: ִ  HEBREW POINT HIRIQ
05B5: ֵ  HEBREW POINT TSERE
05B6: ֶ  HEBREW POINT SEGOL
05B7: ַ  HEBREW POINT PATAH
05B8: ָ  HEBREW POINT QAMATS
05B9: ֹ  HEBREW POINT HOLAM
05BB: ֻ  HEBREW POINT QUBUTS
05BC: ּ  HEBREW POINT DAGESH OR MAPIQ
05BD: ֽ  HEBREW POINT METEG
05BE: ־  HEBREW PUNCTUATION MAQAF
05BF: ֿ  HEBREW POINT RAFE
05C0: ׀  HEBREW PUNCTUATION PASEQ
05C1: ׁ  HEBREW POINT SHIN DOT
05C2: ׂ  HEBREW POINT SIN DOT
05C3: ׃  HEBREW PUNCTUATION SOF PASUQ
05C4: ׄ  HEBREW MARK UPPER DOT
05D0: א  HEBREW LETTER ALEF
05D1: ב  HEBREW LETTER BET
05D2: ג  HEBREW LETTER GIMEL
05D3: ד  HEBREW LETTER DALET
05D4: ה  HEBREW LETTER HE
05D5: ו  HEBREW LETTER VAV
05D6: ז  HEBREW LETTER ZAYIN
05D7: ח  HEBREW LETTER HET
05D8: ט  HEBREW LETTER TET
05D9: י  HEBREW LETTER YOD
05DA: ך  HEBREW LETTER FINAL KAF
05DB: כ  HEBREW LETTER KAF
05DC: ל  HEBREW LETTER LAMED
05DD: ם  HEBREW LETTER FINAL MEM
05DE: מ  HEBREW LETTER MEM
05DF: ן  HEBREW LETTER FINAL NUN
05E0: נ  HEBREW LETTER NUN
05E1: ס  HEBREW LETTER SAMEKH
05E2: ע  HEBREW LETTER AYIN
05E3: ף  HEBREW LETTER FINAL PE
05E4: פ  HEBREW LETTER PE
05E5: ץ  HEBREW LETTER FINAL TSADI
05E6: צ  HEBREW LETTER TSADI
05E7: ק  HEBREW LETTER QOF
05E8: ר  HEBREW LETTER RESH
05E9: ש  HEBREW LETTER SHIN
05EA: ת  HEBREW LETTER TAV
05F0: װ  HEBREW LIGATURE YIDDISH DOUBLE VAV
05F1: ױ  HEBREW LIGATURE YIDDISH VAV YOD
05F2: ײ  HEBREW LIGATURE YIDDISH DOUBLE YOD
05F3: ׳  HEBREW PUNCTUATION GERESH
05F4: ״  HEBREW PUNCTUATION GERSHAYIM